O.k., the drink we're about to make is called a Pink Limon.
We're going to serve this up in a martini glass.
So put some ice and water in there and let it sit while you're making your drink and it'll be nice and cold.
Alright we're going to measure out one and a half ounces of Bacardi Limon, our lemon flavored rum.
And we're going to follow that up with two ounces of sour mix.
And next we'll add a half ounce of cranberry juice.
Let me add a little bit more than that, make sure it gets nice and pink.
Alright, now we're going to shake it up, get everything nice and cold.
Go ahead and pour out your ice water and get your strainer, pour it in, very full.
And that is a Pink Limon.
Bottoms up.